So friends, the latest update from ICC Bank is
that you can now
open a zero-balance account online from home.
You can
also complete your KYC through video KYC.
To open this account, you must have a
PAN card or Aadhaar card.
You must be between 18 and 35 years old.
You must maintain a zero balance in this account.
You will receive an exemption of ₹50,000 and
purchase protection of ₹50,000.
You will also have the facility of cardless cash withdrawal.
You will
also have access to internet banking, ATM, and checkbook.
If you make any purchases online with this account, the
bank will offer you up to 1% discount. For example, you
can get a 1% discount by submitting a spoon-top or Big Basket.
We have provided the link to open this account
in the description. You can go there and open this account.
If
you still have any problems opening your account,
You can also fill out an account opening form
so that a bank
representative can call you and
help you open the account.